<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Julie Kallini</title>
    <description>This is the official website of Julie Kallini.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 11:44:05 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 11:44:05 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.6</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Owning 7 Phones at Once</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;No, I don’t &lt;em&gt;actually&lt;/em&gt; own 7 phones. But working on this website lead me to a
discovery about how I could simulate having several devices at once.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jacobtomlinson/carte-noire&quot;&gt;Carte Noire&lt;/a&gt; is a beautiful theme,
but, like most Jekyll themes, it is tailored to hosting blogs. Since I’m building
my website mainly to host my resume and portfolio, I’ve been working directly with
&lt;strong&gt;HTML&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;CSS&lt;/strong&gt; to achieve the look I want, rather than simply using Markdown.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;dealing-with-configuration-changes&quot;&gt;Dealing with Configuration Changes&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I was editing the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;About Me&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; section of my homepage, I wanted to ensure that my
page was &lt;strong&gt;mobile friendly&lt;/strong&gt;, and that the images and text would be displayed nicely
on mobile devices. At first, I had to push my changes in order to view the updated
website on my phone. I noticed that my image would trail off of the “About Me” card:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../../../../images/screenshot1.jpeg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was getting pretty troublesome trying to debug the mobile display without being
able to test it before pushing. I dabbled with some solutions that involved running
my Mac’s localhost on my iPhone, but it turns out that there’s an even better answer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;chrome-devtools&quot;&gt;Chrome DevTools&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This probably comes as no surprise for anyone who’s done some web development already,
but &lt;strong&gt;Chrome DevTools&lt;/strong&gt; blew my mind when I started using it.
Chrome DevTools allows you to view and interact with the HTML and CSS of basically
any website. With a simple press of &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;F12&lt;/code&gt;, I’m taken to a new pane where I can view my
website on a range of devices, not just an iPhone! Now I can easily diagnose layout
issues on lower-resolution displays locally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../../../../images/screenshot2.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So no, I don’t really own 7 phones, but I think this has been a worthwhile discovery
for me anyway.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 05:29:19 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/08/19/owning-7-phones-at-once/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/08/19/owning-7-phones-at-once/</guid>
        
        <category>phones</category>
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
        <category>devices</category>
        
        <category>website</category>
        
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>HelpQ</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;preface&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preface&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;HelpQ&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is an &lt;strong&gt;Android app&lt;/strong&gt; that I developed at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/careers/students-and-grads/students&quot;&gt;Facebook University (FBU) for Engineering&lt;/a&gt; during the summer of 2019. As an intern at FBU, I
participated in three weeks of mobile development training in Android prior to working on HelpQ with my teammates, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/cassandra-cabrera-7b7582159/&quot;&gt;Cassandra Cabrera&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/lonitra/&quot;&gt;Loni Tra&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When coming up with app ideas, I considered my experiences as a student and an intern at FBU. In particular,
I thought that the mobile development training course would have greatly benefited from an automated help queue to streamline communication between students who need help and administrators who are available to answer questions. When I suggested this idea to my teammates and mentors, they agreed that we should develop this app as our project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;about-the-app&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the App&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../../../../images/helpq_logo.png&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HelpQ&lt;/strong&gt; is an app that revamps the CodePath training that FBU for Engineering interns experience during the first three weeks of their internships by facilitating smoother communication between students and administrators.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HelpQ’s most fundamental function is to make students’ questions more &lt;strong&gt;organized&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;readily available&lt;/strong&gt; for admins to answer. Admins can easily see students’ questions in order by date and priority on the queue.
Students who have been waiting the longest appear at the top of the queue, so the admin can’t miss them!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All previously answered questions are stored on a &lt;strong&gt;searchable&lt;/strong&gt; board that is available to all students. If a student has a question that has already been asked, they can easily find its answer without having to post a new question on the queue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If an admin sees many questions on a similar topic, they can create a &lt;strong&gt;workshop&lt;/strong&gt; for students to attend. Students can see all the workshops in reverse-chronological order and easily sign up for them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are only a few of the features that HelpQ has to offer! To learn more about HelpQ’s functionality, view the project on &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/FBUAndroidTeam/HelpQ&quot;&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt;, or continue reading below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;video-walkthroughs&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Video Walkthroughs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s a walkthrough of implemented features:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;student-walkthrough&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Student Walkthrough:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/FBUAndroidTeam/HelpQ/master/helpq_walkthrough1.gif&quot; style=&quot;border-radius: 20px;&quot; title=&quot;Student Walkthrough&quot; width=&quot;&quot; alt=&quot;Student Walkthrough&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;admin-walkthrough&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Admin Walkthrough:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/FBUAndroidTeam/HelpQ/master/helpq_walkthrough2.gif&quot; title=&quot;Admin Walkthrough&quot; style=&quot;border-radius: 20px;&quot; width=&quot;&quot; alt=&quot;Admin Walkthrough&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GIFs created with &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cockos.com/licecap/&quot;&gt;LiceCap&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;comprehensive-list-of-completed-features&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comprehensive List of Completed Features&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;loginsign-up&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Login/Sign up&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Students and admins can login with &lt;strong&gt;Facebook&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;When a student signs up, they are prompted to choose their admin.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The current signed in user is persisted across app restarts.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;App uses &lt;strong&gt;Parse&lt;/strong&gt; as its backend to store user data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;queue&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Queue&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Students can &lt;strong&gt;ask questions&lt;/strong&gt; on the queue.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Select priority, which indicates the severity of their issue (blocking, stretch, or curiosity).&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Select type of help needed (written, or in person).&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Students can delete their own questions from the queue.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Admins can &lt;strong&gt;delete&lt;/strong&gt; questions from the queue.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Admins can &lt;strong&gt;submit answers&lt;/strong&gt; to questions that have requested written help.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Questions on the queue are sorted based on priority and date.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Live estimated wait times&lt;/strong&gt; are provided.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Displayed for each priority when asking a question.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Displayed for each question on the queue.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;student-to-student-help&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Student-to-Student Help&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Students can like and reply to other students’ questions on the queue.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;If a student likes a question, it will also appear in their inbox when answered.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Admins can verify replies to other student’s questions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;inbox-and-board&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Inbox and Board&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Students and admins can see a board of all students’ &lt;strong&gt;previously answered questions&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Students have an inbox of all the questions they have previously asked, with their answers.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Admins can choose to make a question’s answer &lt;strong&gt;private&lt;/strong&gt;, so it will only appear in that student’s inbox.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;fuzzy-search&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fuzzy Search&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fuzzy search&lt;/strong&gt; is available on queue, board, and inbox.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Search queries only yield results with a significant match.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Query results update with every character change.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;workshops&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Workshops&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Admins can create workshops, indicating the topic, time, and location.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Students can sign up for workshops.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Students are reminded 15 minutes before a workshop begins with a &lt;strong&gt;notification&lt;/strong&gt;.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Students have a settings page where they can change the preferred time to 5 or 10 minutes.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;enrolled-students&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Enrolled Students&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Admins can view a list of their own students, along with all unanswered questions for each student.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;profile&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Profile&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Students and admins can see their profile page with their Facebook picture.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;An admin’s profile displays the number of questions they have answered.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;A student’s profile displays the number of answers that have been verified.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;additional-features&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Additional Features&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In-app notification&lt;/strong&gt; badges are displayed on tabs with new messages.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;New items are marked in the queue, board, and inbox.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pull down to refresh is available on all pages.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Queue, board, and inbox items all display custom animations.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;User interactions have sound effects.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Landscape orientation is available.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;credits&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Credits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/xdrop/fuzzywuzzy&quot;&gt;JavaWuzzy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 11:41:19 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/projects/2019/08/16/helpq/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/projects/2019/08/16/helpq/</guid>
        
        <category>projects</category>
        
        <category>facebook</category>
        
        <category>android</category>
        
        
        <category>projects</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My First Blog Post</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my first professional website!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was gifted the ownership of my own domain name as a going away present from my amazing Facebook managers &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/huntermonk/&quot;&gt;Hunter Monk&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/seong-wan-song-a08b5645/&quot;&gt;Seong Wan Song&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m learning to use &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/code&gt; to get my site up and running, so stay tuned for updates!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 08:31:19 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/08/15/my-first-blog-post/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/08/15/my-first-blog-post/</guid>
        
        <category>first</category>
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
        <category>website</category>
        
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Maze Adventures</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;preface&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preface&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Maze Adventures&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is a &lt;strong&gt;Unity3D&lt;/strong&gt; game that I developed at Princeton Summer Programming
Experiences during the summer of 2018. I was one of 16 first-year Computer Science
students chosen to work on an independent project with Princeton faculty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In preparation for creating the final game shown below, I researched and studied various maze
generating and solving algorithms, and implemented simulations of these algorithms in Unity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;View the project on &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jkallini/MazeAdventures&quot;&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt;, or play the game
&lt;a href=&quot;https://juliekallini.com/MazeAdventures/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;about-the-game&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Game&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../../../../images/title.png&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; style=&quot;border-radius:20px;&quot; alt=&quot;Maze Adventures&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In &lt;strong&gt;Maze Adventures&lt;/strong&gt;, you play as a lonely pill trying to escape a dangerous maze.
Before the game starts, you are greeted by a menu screen that allows you to input the size of the
maze you would like to play in. Your maze can be as small as a tiny 5 by 5 grid, or as large as a 30 by
30 labyrinth!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each time you start a new game, Maze Adventures uses a &lt;a href=&quot;http://weblog.jamisbuck.org/2011/1/12/maze-generation-recursive-division-algorithm&quot;&gt;recursive division maze generation algorthim&lt;/a&gt; to
create a &lt;strong&gt;unique, random maze at runtime&lt;/strong&gt;. So no memorizing the paths here! The number of unique levels
is infinite, which means endless fun for the player.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This game isn’t &lt;em&gt;just&lt;/em&gt; about getting through the maze, though. The evil Glowies have locked your
Pill friends in rooms, and hid the keys all over the maze. You have to find the keys and unlock all of
the rooms before you can leave the maze!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Glowies, the keys, and the rooms are distributed randomly across the maze using &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cemyuksel.com/cyCodeBase/soln/poisson_disk_sampling.html&quot;&gt;Poisson disk sampling&lt;/a&gt;. This ensures that they will be in new
positions every time you start a new level, but the Glowies won’t be able to gang up on you in one section of
the maze.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;completed-features&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Completed Features&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;menu-and-maze-generation&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Menu and Maze Generation&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Main menu screen allows the player to input the desired dimensions of the maze.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;During a level, the player can pause at any time, and return to the main menu.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Random mazes generated at runtime.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Recursive division maze generation algorithm coded in Unity from scratch.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Poisson disk distribution used to scatter rooms, enemies, health, and keys across the maze with uniform randomness.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Exactly same number of keys and rooms are generated.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Objects are placed randomly but cannot spawn in the same locations.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;characters&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Characters&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Player can rotate in the direction of the cursor and fire projectiles on click.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bomb enemies created.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Can follow the player’s transform and inflict damage upon contact.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Can drop bombs that damage the player and destroy walls within their blast radius.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fire enemies created.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Can shoot projectiles in the direction of the player’s transform that inflict damage.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;assets-animations-and-ui&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Assets, Animations, and UI&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;All 3D models and animations created from scratch in Unity.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Player and enemies flash while taking damage.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Player’s health bar decreases when the player is damaged and increases after the player finds health.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;All enemies have individual health bars.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fire enemies animated with spinning projectiles.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Collectible items rotate.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Player and enemies explode upon death.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;directions&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Use &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;WASD&lt;/code&gt; to move around. Your cursor indicates the direction you want to shoot. Left-click to shoot a
pellet. If you have a key, you can use it to unlock a room. Stand next to the door of the room and press
&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;return&lt;/code&gt; to unlock the door. Once all rooms have been opened, navigate to the exit in the top-right corner
of the maze.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;video-walkthrough&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Video Walkthrough&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/355216571?autoplay=1&amp;amp;loop=1&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;479&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; style=&quot;text-align: center&quot; allow=&quot;autoplay; fullscreen&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;player&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Player&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../../../../images/player.png&quot; width=&quot;80&quot; alt=&quot;Player&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;key&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Key&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Collect these keys to unlock rooms!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../../../../images/key.png&quot; width=&quot;80&quot; alt=&quot;Key&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;room&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Room&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These are rooms where your fellow Pills are trapped!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../../../../images/room.png&quot; width=&quot;230&quot; alt=&quot;Room&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;bomb-glowy&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bomb Glowy&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bomb Glowies can follow you around. Don’t let them touch you!
They can also drop bombs when they get close to you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../../../../images/red_enemy.png&quot; width=&quot;80&quot; alt=&quot;Bomb Glowy&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;bomb&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bomb&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bombs are dropped by Bomb Glowies. Bombs can break walls, which makes it easier to get
through the maze. But don’t be too close to the bombs when they explode!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../../../../images/bomb.png&quot; width=&quot;70&quot; alt=&quot;Bomb&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;fire-glowy&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fire Glowy&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fire Glowies are stationary, but they can shoot fire balls at you! They also take
twice as much damage as Bomb Glowies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../../../../images/fire_enemy.png&quot; width=&quot;150&quot; alt=&quot;Fire Glowy&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;heart&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Heart&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hearts replenish some of your health. You can find them by searching the maze,
or by defeating Glowies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../../../../images/heart.png&quot; width=&quot;70&quot; alt=&quot;Heart&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;credits&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Credits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://gregschlom.com/devlog/2014/06/29/Poisson-disc-sampling-Unity.html&quot;&gt;Poisson-disc sampling in Unity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 11:48:27 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/projects/2018/07/20/maze-adventures/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/projects/2018/07/20/maze-adventures/</guid>
        
        <category>projects</category>
        
        <category>unity</category>
        
        <category>SPE</category>
        
        
        <category>projects</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
